<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Welcome to My Personal Blog on Osazee's Blog</title><link>http://localhost:3000/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to My Personal Blog on Osazee's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.147.8</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:3000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://localhost:3000/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:28:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:3000/contact/</guid><description>Get in touch - lets connect and chat about code, life, or anything in between</description></item><item><title>The Art of Continuous Learning: Embracing the Unknown</title><link>http://localhost:3000/posts/thoughts-on-learning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:15:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:3000/posts/thoughts-on-learning/</guid><description>Personal reflections on the journey of lifelong learning</description></item><item><title>The Evolution of Web Development: From Static to Dynamic</title><link>http://localhost:3000/posts/my-first-tech-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:15:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:3000/posts/my-first-tech-post/</guid><description>Exploring how web development has transformed over the years</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://localhost:3000/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:14:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:3000/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img alt="About me" loading="lazy" src="http://localhost:3000/images/osazee.png">&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="about-me">About me&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>I design, I build, I guide. My work is sacred. My journey is eternal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I see the world as a space where innovation meets purpose—where technology isn’t just built, but shaped to solve problems that matter. I work at the intersection of blockchain, software engineering, and program design, constantly seeking ways to turn ideas into impactful solutions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My journey has been a blend of engineering precision and big-picture thinking—from architecting blockchain-powered products to designing systems that scale, from leading diverse teams to mentoring the next wave of builders. I’ve learned that the most exciting breakthroughs happen where curiosity meets disciplined execution.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>